iza te o nobashite Reach your hands out,
kaze o kirisaite cut through the wind,
onore no chizu o egaite yuke and forge ahead, drawing your own map as you go!
migi mo hidari mo guchaguchahit *#E We can't even tell left from right
areta umi no you na jidai in this tempest-tossed era
kizukiageta kachikan Sae mo Even the values we've honed
kuzuresarou to shita [PAINT] 1f # : I Don't Like Mondays.  : I Don't Like Mondays. rhuthmZone seem ready to crumble
kuzuresaron to shita seem ready to crumble
rashinban no Sashita Saki ga A Is the compass leading us true.
tadashii no ka douka nante or is it leading us astray?
douse dare ni mo wakaranain da Nobody knows for sure!
fukaku iki o suikonde hitomi tojireba Just breathe deep, close your eyes
ukabi agaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi and you'll find your soul guiding the way!
iza te o nobashite Reach your hands out,
kaze o kirisaite cut through the wind,
kurayami o kettobashite and kick away the darkness!
ima boku wa boku no tame ni I'm doing this for myself,
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou 2 * and you're doing this for yourself too, right?
ronore no iro de egaite yuke Forge ahead, painting the world in your own colors!
ke
HEPTEC Edited by fedew Subtitles by HatSubs
J-o-i-n?
Let's all take out Kaido, together!
Order acknowledged!
Master!
Hamlet-sama's totally lost it!
Castle Interior, Fourth Floor Big Cat Cafe
I got you, Master!
Hwuuuh?!
•••
Ya-hoo!
First Son of the Sea, Jinbe! Leave the peanut gallery to me!
Beat the living crap outta Who's-Who!
Poker! You filthy piece of..!
Castle Interior Second Floor Your backup has arrived, samurai!
We're behind Straw Hat all the way!
Castle interior, second floor, checking in. Gifters have switched sides.
How odd...
Y I wonder what happened..
You did it, O-Tama!
O-Nami-chan!
You were amazing, Tama! Your words reached everyone!
Uh-huh, uh-huh!
It was totally worth it, O-Tama!
Thank you, O-Nami-chan!
Mission definitely accomplished!
Oh, yeah! The table's so turned!
You can't be serious... That runt's behind this?!
111 11
That's bad news!
O-Tama!
Holy crap, run!
()
Eat it and die!
The end!
/11
Collier Strike!
You damned...
Son of Judge!
You will not say that name ever again!
Were you part of that team of mad scientists too?!
MADS, ya mean?
Man, that was forever ago.
Check out my bod!
I'mma lay it all out for ya...
I'm acyborg!
Noticed that along time ago!
Oh, crap!
It's Queen's Man-Beast Mode!
Get back!
You noticin' don't matter if ya can't beat me!
Chopper... Mossbrain's gonna make it, right?
Yessirree...
He'll...
He'll be just fine 'n dandy, Sanji.
But, uh... are you gonna make it?
Yeah... Thanks for your concern.
I'll be a-okay!
Baby Geezer Chopper This is a mere side effect (Side Effect of the Rumble Ball) of the Rumble Ball...
We of the Mink Tribe have...
I mean to say, there exists a medicine, passed down within our tribe in Zou.
A medicine so potent that it heals even the most grievous wounds in no time....
But in exchange,
the side effects later will cause him to suffer twice as much as he is now...
I don't know...
Under my discretion, I can't administer it...
Just give me the jab already!
You were listening in?
= We don't got time to think.
There ain't no point in worryin' about what happens to my body later...
...if I can't fight now!
Defections from the Headliners and Gifters to the samurai army...
...number approximately 300!
The order from the girl that took the stage on the Performance Floor
...most likely affected them in some way!
There she is!
It's the brat!
They're after us!
Get a move on, Usopp!
Damn her and her weird tricks!
If we kill her, is that gonna bring the ibunch of guys she's got under her thumb back to their senses?
Crap! They're after Tama!
Gunning for a kid...
And those scumbuckets call themselves pirates!
I'm gonna protect O-Tama!
O-Nami-chan!
Usopp!
I've got some asses to kick! Go on without me!
Here come the Headliners!
Scorpion...
..Death Needle!
Poison!
Nuh?!
You're all sunk! The bunch of yous are already poisoned!
Gaaaahhhh!
Daifugo-kun, thanks!
Yay!
Master!
The operation was ahuge success, Master!
Come, climb aboard!
Horselina-chan, thank you for coming!
Huh?
Let me hop on too, if it's not any trouble! Please!
Master!
UN
I just saw Komachiyo over there, collapsed!
I don't know what's going on...
...but it's about time I got serious.
Blade Pistol!
/11 Fishman Karate:
7 Arabesque Brick Fist!
Shaving!
WHA
Tempest Kick!
1111 11111 1111
"Shaving!"
"Tempest Kick!"
111 ( "111 11 ill
111 "111 11 Should I perhaps call this "Iron Body," then?
Those are techniques from the fighting style in use by Government agents...
The Six Forms.
Come to think of it, I heard a rumor a long time ago...
... that a member of CP9, the Government's secret intelligence agency, escaped from prison.
Strange story, that..
1/1 About an intelligence agent being imprisoned, that is.
N III
And how is it that you remember a scandal like that?
WHOTWHO
WHO WHO
1111.
/111
11/
//
/11
/1
P That escaped agent.
That's right, it's me!
/11
111X/1 Are we acquainted, by chance?
WHO I did see you,
WHO WHO back when I was in CP9,
and you were still a Warlord!
Now, we're both in /totally different situations from then.
I like who I am now..
...but I went through a hell of a lot to get to this point.
All thanks to one single screw-up thirteen years ago...
They used to say I was as promising as the brilliant Rob Lucci!
What that story has to do with me, I haven't the foggiest...
Shut up! Ears open, mouth shut!
WHO WHO
Fang Pistol!
Now there's a Form // I haven't seen before.
I pity/you, but I'm afraid I have nothing to do with you.
Not exactly true!
You did say...
that you're a proud crew member of the Straw Hats, yeah?
That name brings back bitter memories.
Thirteen years ago...
A Devil Fruit in transit aboard a Government ship was stolen.
VMI And two years ago, when Straw Hat Luffy rose to prominence,
I was shocked to learn...
KAXI
...that Straw Hat had eaten the very Gum-Gum Fruit...
...that was stolen from me back then!
Komachiyo...
MA
? He'll be fine!
Yer right, you are!
Giddy up, Horselina-chan!
Roger-dodger, Master!
Leave Komachiyo to us!
Ya mean it?! Thank you!
Daifugo-kun, Gazelleman-kun... please be careful!
Yer both...
...precious friends to me!
G F-r-i-e-n-d-s..!
G Master!
Awwright!
Wait for us, Komachiyo!
Eat my counterattack!
Your ability's really something else..
Yeah...
Normally you don't make friends on the battlefield...
Say, Nami... Speaking of "friends..."
Can you make me your servant again, like before?
What are you talking about?! Not a chance!
Huuuh?!
How's partner sound?
Nami!
There they are! It's the Straw Hats!
Not a step closer!
I'm Nami's partner!
And she's totally got him wrapped around her finger...
Down with Kaido!
Pave the way to victory for Master and the Straw Hats!
Approximately 2,000 have defected.
Castle Interior Guest Parlor And the number of troops blindsided and taken down by them: 2,000!
Meaning, the Animal Kingdom Pirates started with 30,000,
dwindled to 20,000,
lost 2,000 to mutiny, and a further 2,000 to injury,
shrinking our forces even more!
OAO
9 16,000 vs. 9,000!
If the Gifters continue their rampage, the white pieces on the board will multiply.
Which side wins is of no concern to me,
but we must verify his death, no..?
But is it truly him, though?
It would seem that he is.
Regardless... the information he absconded with is out of date.
It poses no threat to the Government.
I disagree... We can't allow precedent to be set...
B That one can flee our organization and yet live.
O Well, that is if he survives.
He fights against...
...the mighty Jinbe.
1/11
ill
1 111 1/11 /
You mean to say... You bear a grudge against Luffy?
To be precise, my grudge is with the Gum-Gum Fruit's thief...
"Red-Haired" Shanks!
Shanks!
It's that thieving scum's fault my life's all screwed up!
Dammit all!
Moonwalk!
Fang Pistol!
1/11
Both the straw hat he wore at the time...
...and the Gum-Gum Fruit were inherited by the kid.
So naturally, I turned my grudge toward him!
Blocking's impossible even with your Color of Arms, huh?
Good choice... Your typical Color of Arms won't save you here!
Though, I'm surprised how quickly you can move on land, Jinbe!
You know... for a Fishman!
I don't believe this...
You do know casual racism against Fishmen is out of style, right?
Don't be mad, now!
WHO
There's something I wanna ask you.
Iron Body!
Prepare yourself, Jinbe!
Fang Flash!
Fishman Jujutsu:
Low Tide...
...Shoulder Throw!
Water Shot!
Shaving!
Oof...
11/1 God damn, you're merciless...
WHOOWHO
Say, why don't you..
...listen to what I got to say, just for a few seconds...
While I was behind bars, I heard this story.
While I was busy being tortured,
they mocked me, told me to pray for salvation..
...to the Sun God, Nika!
He is an ancient, legendary warrior, one that slaves believed...
...would one day set them free.
Did he exist, or was he just someone's fever dream?
A warrior that made people laugh, all the while delivering them from suffering...
My time in prison felt so endless...
...I actually clung to that bizarre legend of theirs!
"Save me!" I thought to myself. "Someone, anyone!"
Why are you telling me all this?
I heard your old crew, the Sun Pirates...
.counted among their ranks former slaves!
VIHA
WHA
Fishman history is all about slavery, isn't it?
The guard who told me about Nika...
...was executed shortly after!
I risked it all to break out, and here I am today!
Is it bad for one's health just to know?
Fascinating, don't ya think?
Tell me what you know!
Finger Pistol!
1111 111
Spots!
WHOS
OCWHO
Fishman Karate:
Shark Crunch!
I've nothing to say to the likes of you!
What the... Did I flip a switch or something?!
Here comes the puncture wound!
Fang Pistol!
///
The hell is up with you?!
Fishman Karate, Secret Art:
Dammit all!
Hey, watch the tail!
Demon Brick Fist!
lf you're going to run your mouth about history...
...you had best be ready for what you're stepping into first!
TO BE CONTINUED